<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <link>http://verizon.github.io/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://verizon.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Another Article</title>
      <link>http://verizon.github.io/blog/another-article/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://verizon.github.io/blog/another-article/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Bacon ipsum dolor amet rump salami flank tongue. Boudin meatloaf alcatra, andouille kielbasa hamburger kevin pork belly venison. Tenderloin jowl picanha strip steak, hamburger t-bone drumstick. Fatback beef sausage meatball t-bone pastrami. Ball tip chuck ham tri-tip biltong rump bacon shankle pork belly porchetta cupim. Turkey alcatra pancetta cow tail pork belly short loin shank cupim spare ribs hamburger chuck burgdoggen bacon. Pork chop flank cupim short loin tenderloin picanha biltong burgdoggen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Swine meatloaf ribeye short ribs. Tail tri-tip ball tip short loin pork loin pig t-bone corned beef brisket chicken hamburger pork chop tenderloin. Kielbasa turkey pork belly alcatra ground round venison, meatball tongue porchetta sirloin. Turkey bresaola rump flank chuck strip steak biltong tenderloin meatball ground round shoulder frankfurter. Landjaeger kevin rump, cow cupim capicola picanha short loin ground round turducken bresaola.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Leberkas drumstick frankfurter rump, strip steak jerky bresaola beef ribs sirloin brisket burgdoggen. Rump turkey beef, fatback chuck flank spare ribs leberkas. Capicola ball tip short ribs t-bone swine. Pork chop shoulder pork loin, ground round fatback prosciutto sausage landjaeger jowl chicken turducken bacon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Doner brisket alcatra chuck t-bone chicken. Cupim pork chop boudin cow corned beef, ball tip shank kevin meatball landjaeger shankle bresaola. Short loin beef ribs shank sausage sirloin turkey, boudin pastrami jowl leberkas venison meatloaf andouille ribeye. Beef turkey jerky prosciutto jowl. Prosciutto hamburger boudin capicola.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Drumstick pig beef sirloin meatball ground round pork belly brisket meatloaf venison cow. Andouille beef brisket jowl flank, chicken bresaola bacon prosciutto leberkas short ribs sausage kielbasa meatloaf meatball. Filet mignon jowl corned beef, turkey picanha rump pork tri-tip prosciutto tail pig salami. Pork belly hamburger turducken turkey beef jowl. Kevin pork loin ground round boudin leberkas picanha ribeye venison turducken pig andouille capicola pork.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Some Exciting Article</title>
      <link>http://verizon.github.io/blog/some-exciting-article/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://verizon.github.io/blog/some-exciting-article/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Bacon ipsum dolor amet rump salami flank tongue. Boudin meatloaf alcatra, andouille kielbasa hamburger kevin pork belly venison. Tenderloin jowl picanha strip steak, hamburger t-bone drumstick. Fatback beef sausage meatball t-bone pastrami. Ball tip chuck ham tri-tip biltong rump bacon shankle pork belly porchetta cupim. Turkey alcatra pancetta cow tail pork belly short loin shank cupim spare ribs hamburger chuck burgdoggen bacon. Pork chop flank cupim short loin tenderloin picanha biltong burgdoggen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Swine meatloaf ribeye short ribs. Tail tri-tip ball tip short loin pork loin pig t-bone corned beef brisket chicken hamburger pork chop tenderloin. Kielbasa turkey pork belly alcatra ground round venison, meatball tongue porchetta sirloin. Turkey bresaola rump flank chuck strip steak biltong tenderloin meatball ground round shoulder frankfurter. Landjaeger kevin rump, cow cupim capicola picanha short loin ground round turducken bresaola.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Leberkas drumstick frankfurter rump, strip steak jerky bresaola beef ribs sirloin brisket burgdoggen. Rump turkey beef, fatback chuck flank spare ribs leberkas. Capicola ball tip short ribs t-bone swine. Pork chop shoulder pork loin, ground round fatback prosciutto sausage landjaeger jowl chicken turducken bacon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Doner brisket alcatra chuck t-bone chicken. Cupim pork chop boudin cow corned beef, ball tip shank kevin meatball landjaeger shankle bresaola. Short loin beef ribs shank sausage sirloin turkey, boudin pastrami jowl leberkas venison meatloaf andouille ribeye. Beef turkey jerky prosciutto jowl. Prosciutto hamburger boudin capicola.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Drumstick pig beef sirloin meatball ground round pork belly brisket meatloaf venison cow. Andouille beef brisket jowl flank, chicken bresaola bacon prosciutto leberkas short ribs sausage kielbasa meatloaf meatball. Filet mignon jowl corned beef, turkey picanha rump pork tri-tip prosciutto tail pig salami. Pork belly hamburger turducken turkey beef jowl. Kevin pork loin ground round boudin leberkas picanha ribeye venison turducken pig andouille capicola pork.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Talks</title>
      <link>http://verizon.github.io/talks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://verizon.github.io/talks/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h1 id=&#34;talks&#34;&gt;Talks&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many, many of the systems we use here at OnCue are built on top of open source technology, and we are large proponents of OSS as a general rule. This however does come with a few hard realities: Verizon is a large company and we have to be legally complient with software licensing, and open-source projects are no different. As a general rule of thumb the following licenses are suitibly permissive to allow use within the company.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>